A Guide to the Records of Frank Ix & Sons
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Records of Frank Ix & Sons, Inc. 1968-1995
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11577
80 boxes, ca. 60 cubic feet.
Administrative Information
Access
Shelved in remote storage facility; researchers should request 24 hours in advance of desired use.
Acquisition Information
Gift: Frank Ix and Company; 531 Ware Street, Charlottesville, Va. 22902; 2000 January 14. Boxes 1-58, 61-62 received 2000 January 14. Box 59 received 2000 January 26. Boxes 62-76 received 2000 February 2. Boxes 77-80 received 2002 October 2.
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains employee files; personnel files; affirmative action files; human resources department subject files; memoranda and other records of personnel manager John Todd; together with some financial and legal papers.
Contents List
- Ledgers, Cash Books, etc. (Box 1)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1980 (Box 2)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1981 (part) (Box 3)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1981 (cont.)-1982 (part) (Box 4)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1982 (cont.)-1983 (Box 5)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1984 (Box 6)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1985 (Box 7)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1986 (part) (Box 8)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1986 (cont.)-1987 (Box 9)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records, A-D 1988-1989 (Box 10)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records, E-Y, including 1987 monthly manufacturing reports 1987-1989 (Box 11)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1990 (Box 12)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1991 (Box 13)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1992 (Box 14)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records, including 1991 personal expenses 1991-1993 (part) (Box 15)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records, including 1992 personal expenses and 1980-1982 annual reports 1980-1983, 1992-1993 (Box 16)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1994 (Box 17)
- John Todd, Memoranda and Other Records 1995 (Box 18)
- Executive Committee Meetings & Financial Reports July 1987-Oct 1989 (Box 19)
- Executive Committee Meetings & Financial Reports Nov 1989-Sep 1991 (Box 20)
- Executive Committee Meetings & Financial Reports Oct 1991-Oct 1993 (Box 21)
- Executive Committee Meetings & Financial Reports and special reports: "Department Review," "Corporate Development" and Preliminary Plan Books" 1988-1990, 1993-May 1995 (Box 22)
- Tax Returns 1948-1972 (Box 23)
- Labor Process Manuals (Box 24)
- Company Housing Deeds and Other Legal Documents (Box 25)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, A-B (Box 26)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, C-D (Box 27)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, E-H (Box 28)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, I-P (photographs) (Box 29)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, P(cont.)-S (Box 30)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, S-T (Box 31)
- Human Resources Department Subject Files, U-W, plus Annual Personnel Reports (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Employee and Health Manuals & Reports (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Employee Information, including Reports to Virginia Employment Commission, Affirmative Action files, and Employee Appreciation files (Box 34)
- Employee and Wage Data and Affirmative Action Files--Lexington plant (Box 35)
- Affirmative Action Files--Charlottesville plant (Box 36)
- Personnel Files (inactive supervisory staff?)Barnwell, Gloria-Tripp, John (Box 37)
- Personnel Files (inactive supervisory staff?) Tysinger, F.-Young, Gene and (active supervisory staff?) Bates, John-Sink, Brian (Box 38)
- Personnel Files (active supervisory staff?) Sink, Gideon-Yon, Duom, and (active female) Banks, Barbara-Z, and (inactive female) Bruce, Daphine-Johnson, Emma (Box 39)
- Personnel Files (inactive female) Johnson, Flora-Vaughan, Roberta and Personnel Files (inactive) Allen, Antrone-Collins, Davis (Box 40)
- Personnel Files (inactive), Collins, Kenneth-Dudley, Sherry and Employee Data & Reports 1989-1995 (Box 41)
- Personnel Files (inactive), Eldridge, Ellen-Harris, John (Box 42)
- Personnel Files (inactive), Harris, Virginia-Loving, Calvin (Box 43)
- Personnel Files (inactive), McClary, Shirley-Pils, Helmuth (Box 44)
- Personnel Files (inactive), Pineda, Neftali-Smith, Jesse (Box 45)
- Personnel Files (inactive), Smith, Kenneth-Williams, Percy (Box 46)
- Personnel files (active), A-Carrick, Huston (Box 47)
- Personnel files (active), Carroll, Edith-Dunning, Tina (Box 48)
- Personnel files (active), Dusenbury, Roland-Gibson, Stacy (Box 49)
- Personnel files (active), Gillen, Alice-Hunt, Debbi (Box 50)
- Personnel files (active), Hunt, Melinda-Leeth, Dwayne; and Affirmative Action Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 51)
- Personnel files (active), Lem, Moany-Mounce, Peggy (Box 52)
- Personnel files (active), Murph, Mary-Reeves, Concepcion (Box 53)
- Personnel files (active), Reich, Jeff-Spaugh, Tami (Box 54)
- Personnel files (active), Spaul, Chad-Vuth, Andy (Box 55)
- Personnel files (active), Wachob, Deborah-Z (Box 56)
- Employee Files, [series] "1968-1974," A-C 1968-1974 (Box 57)
- Employee Files, [series] "1968-1974," D-He 1968-1974 (Box 58)
- Employee Files, [series] "1968-1974," Hi-M 1968-1974 (Box 59)
- Employee Files, [series] "1968-1974," N-S 1968-1974 (Box 60)
- Employee Files, [series] "1968-1974," T-Z 1968-1974 (Box 61)
- Personnel Files, [series] "Prior to 1992," A-K (Box 62)
- Personnel Files, [series] "Prior to 1992," L-R (Box 63)
- Personnel Files, [series] "Prior to 1992," S-Z (Box 64)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], A-Cre (Box 65)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Cri-Ge (Box 66)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Gi-Lam (Box 67)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Lan-Pa (Box 68)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Pe-Si (Box 69)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Sm-To (Box 70)
- Personnel Files, [series undated], Tr-Z and [part of another series/supervisors?], A-D (Box 71)
- Personnel Files, "1992," A-W 1992 (Box 72)
  note: original box was marked "women," but men are included
- Personnel Files, [series] "1978-1985," A-C 1978-1985 (Box 73)
- Personnel Files, [series] "1978-1985," D-I 1978-1985 (Box 74)
- Personnel Files, [series] "1978-1985," J-R 1978-1985 (Box 75)
  (S-Z not received)
- Applications for Employment, "1968-1974," A-Z 1968-1974 (Box 76)
- Personnel Files, [series] "Prior to 1992" (inactive females), A-Y [1968?]-[1991?] (Box 77)
  also Patricia Barker and Thomas Barker
- "Labor Law / Union Avoidance" (Box 78)
- John Todd: 1980 Union Campaign 1980 (Box 79)
- E.E.O.C. Legal Cases (Box 80)